th8.us 2012-09-20

# Th8.us: URL trimming made simple.

**PRIVACY POLICY FOR TH8.US**  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support@th8.us.

At Th8.us, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Th8.us and how it is used.

**ADVERTISEMENTS ON REDIRECTED URLS**  
To help cover our hosting costs, Th8.us displays Amazon, Adbrite, or Google Adsense advertisements in an iFrame above most URLs shortened through our service. If you do not want these ads displayed on your website(s), please email a list of all your domains to support@th8.us and we will promptly modify all short URLs for your domains to forward directly to the destination page using an HTTP 301 redirect, without advertising.

**PUBLICATION OF SHORTENED URLS**  
All URLs shortened through Th8.us should be considered public, and we may in some point in the future make our databases publicly accessible, including the short URLs, long URLs, and dates of creation. If you have shortened URLs that you want removed from our database, please email the list to support@th8.us with some proof that you created them or they reveal personal information about you or someone you know.

**LOG FILES**  
Like many other Web sites, Th8.us makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS**  
Th8.us does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DOUBLECLICK DART COOKIE**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Th8.us.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Th8.us and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense  
Adbrite  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Th8.us send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Th8.us has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Th8.us's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
